Guide to the Ian P. Watt Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-106
  - [Other Projects]
    - Myth 4, Don Quixote (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Myth 6, Robinson Crusoe (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - English 35, Defoe (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Myth 6, Vico and Herder, Notes (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Myth 6, Vico and Herder, Xeroxes (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Myth 6, Robinson Crusoe, Xeroxes (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Myth 6, Rousseau and Crusoe (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Myth 6, Text [Current] (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Myth 6, Tirso (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Myth 6.4, Don Juan, Notes (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Myth 6, Goethe: Faust, Notes (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Goethe"361 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Myth 6, Vico and Herder, Drafts (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Myth 6, Goethe and Byron (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Myth 6.4, to add (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Myth 6.4 Zorilla, Notes and Drafts (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Myth 6.4, Don Juan (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Myth 6.5, Don Quixote (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Myth 6.5, Don Quixote, Notes and Drafts (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Myth 6.5, Don Quixote, Xeroxes (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Faust Xeroxes (Marlowe) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Notes for Faust [1988] (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Myth 1; Witchcraft Notes etc. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Myth 1; Offprints"Magic (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Myth 1; Faust (used) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Recently considered Xeroxes (Faust) [1] (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Recently considered Xeroxes (Faust) [2] (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Recently considered Xeroxes (Faust) [3] (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Myth 1; Recently considered Xeroxes (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Books on Faust Story (Xeroxes) (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Myth 1, My Notes: Luther, Magic etc. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Myth 1, Offprints: Education (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Myth 1; Offprints: Contract Law (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Myth 1; Konneker Article (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Myth 1; Offprints, History (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Myth 1; Luther Period (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Myth 1; Faust Xeroxes [not used] (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Faust 1988 [unused and used notes] (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Don Juan III, Photostats (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Modern Robinson Crusoe"Tournier [Xeroxes etc.] (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Tournier, My Notes. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Don Quixote, Illustrations (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Don Quixote, Drafts (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Myth II, Text and Drafts (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote [1988] (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote (current jottings) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote [Xeroxes not used] (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote (Xeroxes not used, Section 1"3] (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote, Notes to add or consider. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote [Xeroxes to use?] (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote [Xeroxes, not quoted] (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote, Notes, not quoted (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Myth II, Don Quixote, Notes, not quoted (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Robinson Crusoe: Numbers (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Individualism"Articles: Concept (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Individualism"History (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - After the Romantics, Mann's Faustus (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Myth VII.4 Don Juan (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Myth VII.4 [to use] (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Myth VII"Robinson Crusoe (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Myth VII.1 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Myth VII.2 Last Section and Notes (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Numbers"Don Quixote (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Myth VII.1 Current Notes, Agenda (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Myth VII.4 Don Quixote (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Faust"Numbers (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Myth VII, [Early Draft] (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Don Quixote, Notes (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Library Books"Mine Stanford (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Readers Subscription (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Watt: Restoration & Augustan Prose (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Provostial Committee [current] (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Individualism, current Agenda (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Myth, Correspondence [not current] (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Myth, German Books (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Myth VII.2 Current Notes to add (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Grzegorczyk, Marzena (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Myth VII. 1, 2; Perhaps to use (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Myth VII.5, Notes (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Myth VII.5, Notes [2] (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Myth VII.1 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Myth 1; For Translation (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Myth"Faust, Notes (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Myth VI.4 Notes to use (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Myth VII not needed (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Myth; Don Quixote revised [1987] (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Myth 2, Whiting (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote revised [1988] (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Myth 3, Mercedarians (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Faust, Top Copy (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Faust, Palermo Draft (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Santa Cruz Talk"Notes (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Marlowe's Faustus, Dave Riggs' Copy (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Myth 1.1 Original Faust, Notes and Xeroxes (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Marlowe's Faustus, current Notes (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Marlowe's Faustus, Palermo Final Version (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Trustees Talk"1970 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Myth, Toronto Version (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Montery Talk (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Faustus, PAPC 1981 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Faustus, Drafts, PAPC (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Faust"Indianapolis (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Faust"Housten (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Faust"Indiana Offprints (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Faust, Palermo, Buttitta (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Santa Cruz Paper, Marlowe's Faustus (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Talk 1981 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Notes on Faust Lecture (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Myth I.2a (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Myth 1, Literacy, Books etc. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Myth 1, Offprints, Marlowe (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - The Devil, Offprints (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Faust, San Diego Version (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Marlowe's Faust, Bloomington Drafts (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Faust, Xeroxes 1987 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Marlowe's Faust, early (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Myth 1.3, Death (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Faust Bibliography (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Myth 1.4 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Myth 1, Historic Faustus, Offprints (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Myth 1, Faust, Used Xeroxes (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Myth 1, Marlowe and the Myth, Used Xeroxes (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Myth 1.4 Marlowe (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Myth 1, Faust Myth, Offprints (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Myth 1, Magic: Butler, Offprints (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Myth 1, Faust and Luther, Offprints (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Myth 1, Faust, Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Myth 1, 2.c Faust (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Myth 1, Faust, Notes (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Myth 1, 3a Faust, Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Myth 1, 3b Faust, Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Myth 1, 3.4 Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Myth 1, 3c, Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Myth 1, Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Myth 1, early Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Myth IV, recent Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Myth VII, recent Xeroxes (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Myth 1, Late Text (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, late Text (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Myth 3, Don Juan, early Drafts (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Myth 5, Bellhouse Notes (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Myth 7, Late Drafts (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Myth, Introduction, Notes (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Myth, Former Titles (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Myth, Faust, Notes (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Myth 6, Goethe's Faust (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Myth 6, Goethe's Faust, Final Xeroxes (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Myth 6, Goethe, Gauss Texts (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Myth 7, Current Notes to add (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Myth 6, Late Drafts (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Myth 7, 20th.Century Fausts (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Myth 7, Faust, Mann Notes (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Myth 7, Faust (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Myth 7, Dr. Faustus, Mann Notes (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Myth 7, Don Quixote (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Xeroxes (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Draft [Sept. 1988] (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Draft [Dec. 1988] (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Draft (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Draft (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Myth, Don Quixote, Bibliography, not current (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Myth 2, Don Quixote, Draft [Aug.1988] (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Myth 1, final Draft (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Myth, Cambridge University Press, Questionnaire (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Myth, Acknowledgments, not current (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Myth, Xeroxes and Notes (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Myth, University of California Press (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Myth, Editorial Comment, Letters, etc. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Myth, Cambridge University Press, Letters (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Myth, Preface (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Myth, Notes on Copy (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Myth, Preface Copies (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Myth 1, typed Copy [Aug. 1988] (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Myth 1, Marlowe, Notes (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Myth, Acknowledgments (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Myth, Mark Handeler Text (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Myth, The four Myths (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Myth as such, Xeroxes (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Myth, Ivanhoe, Levi"Strauss (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Myth, Bibliography (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Myth, Individualism, etc. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Myth, current Notes (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Myth, Individualism, Plans and Comments (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Myth, Quotes, Titles, Projects (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Myth, biographical Offprints (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Myth 1, Faust, Draft [Sept. 1988] (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Myth, Chapter 1, Draft [Aug. 1988] (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Myth 1.4, Materials, not used (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Myth 1, Pagination (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Myth 1, current working Notes (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Myth 4, Robinson Crusoe, Iconography (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Myth, Notes (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Myth, Robinson Crusoe, Illustrations (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Myth, Iconography, Correspondence (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Myth, Faust, Illustrations, pictorial bibliography (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Myth, Faust pictures (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Myth, Gauss, Lecture 2, Notes (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Myth, Gauss II: Copy 2 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Myth, Gauss III: Copy 3 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Myth, Gauss, First Draft (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Myth, Gauss III, working Drafts and Notes (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Myth, Gauss, Chapter III (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Myth, Gauss, Chapter III, Copy 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Myth, Gauss, Chapter III, Copy 3 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Myth, Gauss, Seminar and Correspondence (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Myth, Gauss, Chapter II, Top Copy (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Myth, Gauss, on Robinson Crusoe (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Myth, Faust, Draft (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Myth IV.4. Don Juan, Gauss Versions (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Myth, Gauss III, Materials (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Myth, Gauss I, Top copy (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Myth Book"Toronto Version (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Myth I.1a, Xeroxes and Notes (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Myth I.1b, Xeroxes and Notes (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Myth, Faust, Notes I and II, Xeroxes (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Myth, Faust, Johann Spiess, Notes (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Myth, "The original Georg Faust", Notes (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Myth, Faust, Johann Spiess, Translation and Notes (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Myth, Faust, Drafts (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Myth, Faust, [86 page version] (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Myth I, Gauss [Early Drafts] (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Myth I, Faust, [Final Draft 1989] (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Myth I, Faust, [Parts of Draft] (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Myth I, Faust, [Last Draft] (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Myth, Handler, Bibliography (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Sottisier [1] (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Sottisier [2] (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Sottisier [3] (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-166
  - 134-234 Winter 1990, Conrad (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 240 A Used (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adler, Jeremy. Article, re: Bobrowski (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, George B. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amiens (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anderson Copyright Permissions (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anderson: Current (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anderson: Current Halverson (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson: Current Notes (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anderson: Edwards Article (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anderson, Jane (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, Jane (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Jane (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Jane. 10/30/89 Revision. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Jane 2/12/90 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Anderson, Jane: Later Career -- Xeroxes, notes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Anderson, Jane: Letters, Etc. Xeroxes (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anderson, Jane: Newspaper Cuttings (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Jane: Notes, Used. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Anderson, Jane: Steve Danziz (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Anderson, Jane: Top Copies (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Anderson, Jane: US Department of Justice (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, May 1990 Documents (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Anderson -- Proofs (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anderson: Top Copies, 11/89 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Appiah, Kwame Anthony. "Europe Upside Down". (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Baines, Jocelyn (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - BBC - Open University (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - BBC Talk: Conrad (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Beatty, Jack (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Book Prizes (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bromwich, David. "Stealing and Bounding". (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Carolyn. Correspondence. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cagle, William R. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cambridge Edition of Joseph Conrad: Cup Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cambridge Edition of Joseph Conrad -- Editorial Manual (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cambridge Edition of Joseph Conrad: NEH Reports, etc. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cambridge Edition of Joseph Conrad: Non Current Notes, Xeroxes, etc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cambridge Edition of Joseph Conrad: Sid Reid (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Canterbury Article (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Canterbury Article Documents (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Canterbury Article: Final Proof (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Canterbury: correspondence (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Casement (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chatto & Windus, Ltd.: publishers' correspondence (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Chronology (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Colonialism in Conrad (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Colonialism Talk (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Conrad -- 1990 Exams, etc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Conrad -- 5F Handouts (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conrad and James article: BBC Version (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Conrad and James article: reproductions of their letters (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Conrad and James Essay: Printed Manuscript (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Conrad Bibliography (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Conrad Conference, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Conrad Correspondence: Current (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Conrad: Current Research (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Conrad: English Press Cuttings (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Conrad Holographs: Gosse - Yale and Texas (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Conrad Holographs Works (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Conrad in 19th Century Accounts (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Conrad in 19th Century: Curent Press Correspondence Since Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Conrad in Movies: Offprints (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Conrad In the Nineteenth Century: Paperback Edition (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Conrad, John. Conrad, Borys. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Conrad Later (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Conrad Letters, reproductions. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Conrad Memorabilia (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Conrad -- Miscellaneous for Classes (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Conrad: Movies (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conrad: Nigger of ‘Narcissus' (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Conrad -- Notes on Texts: His Manucripts (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Conrad on Realism (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Conrad Permissions (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Conrad Seminar: Stanford (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Conrad: Stories (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Conrad Talk: London (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Conradiana: Higdon Retrospective (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence -- Conrad, Vol. I, Complimentary Copies (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence re: Jane Article (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Course Xeroxes (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Crankshaw, Edward. Joseph Conrad: some aspects of the art of the novel. New York: Russell and Russell, 1963. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Crompton, John (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - CUP Format: Nostromo, Current Stuff, Editorial (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Current Notes: Joseph Conrad (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - D'Elia, Gaetano. Correspondence, 6/7/91. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Dantzig: Conrad (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Davies, Laurence. NEH Application. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Decline. Current Notes (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Decline. General Offprints. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Decline: Greene. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Decline. Other Influences. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Decline: Personal Note (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Decline: Text (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Decline. Top Copy. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Decline. Virginia Woolf. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Deurbergue, Jean. The Opening of Victory, with note from the author (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Drafts: Preface to Joseph Conrad I, and "Conrad and Late Victorianism" (Conrad Part II) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Editing -- S4P (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Eliot, T.S. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - English, James (Jim) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Enright, D.J. "Bridges and Boundaries" (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Epilogue Notes (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Epstein, Harry on Nostromo (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Errata: Before Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Flam, Jack. "Monet's Way" (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ford, Ford Madox (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Format (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Foster: Manuscript (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Front Matter (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Front Matter -- 1978 version, Working Papers (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Garnett, Edward (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General Articles Relating to Conrad (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gide, Andre (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - H Articles (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Halverson, John. Postcard, 1962. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Harpham, Geoffrey. Conrad and the Grotesque (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hawkins, Hunt (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Heart of Darkness Articles (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Heart of Darkness -- New (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Henkle -- Manuscript Reports (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Higdon, David Leon. Correspondence. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Humanities Center Talk: Writing About Conrad (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Humanities on the Kwai (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Imperialism (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Imperialism and Conrad (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Impressionism (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - International Conference on Conrad: Canterbury, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Jacobs on Conrad, Mainly Chapter 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - James and Conrad, Miscellaneous Notes (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - James, Henry (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - JC I: Acknowledgements (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - JC I: Additions 4 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - JC I: Awards (Publicity) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - JC I, ch.1: Additions I (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - JC I, ch. 4: Additions Five (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - JC I: Corrections (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - JC I: Errata After Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - JC I: Errata Reviews (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - JC I, Nigger of Narcissus: Additions III (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - JC I: Private Letters and Notes (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - JC I: Promotion/Advertisements (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - JC I: Review (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - JC I Reviews: Originals (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - JC I Reviews: Spares (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - JC I: The Row (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - JC I: UC Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - JC II (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - JC II: Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Joseph Conrad Society (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Karl, Frederick R. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Kocowna, B. "Materialy" (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Kolakowski, Lesek. Review of Miller's Anarchism (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Ledger Letters (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Library Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln, Kenneth R. Joseph Conrad: The Comedy of Perception. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Llombreud, Roger: "Arthur Symons: A Critical Biography" (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lord Jim (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Lord Jim Concordance: guilt, shame, etc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Lord Jim Manuscript (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Lothe, EDDA (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - "Loyalty", from Dictionary of the History of Ideas (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Lukacs, Georg on Conrad (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Lynch, John. "The Intervention in Mexico". (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Machak, FBI correspondence (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - McAlindon, Tom. Nostromo (with note). (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - McClure, John (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Meyers, Jeffrey (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Miller, David. "In the thick of it". (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - MLA 1987 Harkness (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Mount, Wendy, Shoe String Press. Correspondence re: Joseph Conrad's "Under Western Eyes" (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Najder Biography -- My Review (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Najder Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Najder Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Najder Manuscript and Notes (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Najder, Zdzislaw: Current (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Najder, Zdzislaw. Joseph Conrad: A Chronicle. Review by Edward Said. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Narrative (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - NEH: Conrad Szczypien (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New Republic Review: Conrad's Letters, Vol. I (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New Republic: Review of Letters: Materials (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Nigger Article -- Correspondence: Permissions (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Nostromo (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Note from Colleague, 4/28/92 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Notes by Readers of Manuscript (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Notes for JC II (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Books on South America (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Notes on Interviews (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Notes on Kirschner, Paul, "Conrad: The Psychologist as Artist" (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Notes to Self on Conrad [Used] (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Otago -- article and correspondence (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Poland (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Publicity, JC I: Format, Dust Jacket (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Raban, Jonathan: Review of In Search of Conrad by Gavin Young (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Raval and Rehana Khan (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Raval, Suresh: correspondence, re: Conrad manuscript (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Research Correspondence (Conrad) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Retinger Letters (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Review of Dale Spender's Mothers of the Novel. Novemeber, 1987. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Review of The Collected Letters of Joseph Conrad, Vol I, ed. Karl and Davies. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Rosenbach Foundation (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers University Press (Not H. Mann) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Schacht, Paul: Victorian Age: The Old and Their Image (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Schneidau. Ezra Pound: The Image and the Real. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Schopenhauer (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Secret Agent (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Secret Agent, Conrad. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Secret Agent Correspondence. Editor: Macmillan. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Secret Agent: Reviews and Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Secret Sharer (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Shadow Line (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Ships, etc. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Skenazy, Paul. Correspondence. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Solidarity, Shame, etc. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Stape, John. Correspondence. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Syllabus for 1993 Conrad Seminar (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Symbolism (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tarnawski, W. Correspondence. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Time (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Time Table (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tolstoy (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Turner, F.M. "Preliminary Bibliography of Readings". (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Typhoon, Conrad. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Typhoon -- Final (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Van Marle, Hans (Box 11, Folder 11)